<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Bird’s Eye View</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Bird’s Eye View</description><image><url>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/img/01chile/01la_serena.jpg</url><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/img/01chile/01la_serena.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Madrid, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/madrid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/madrid/</guid><description>Madrid, Spain August 2022
Capital of Spain Bienvenidos a Madrid! As you step foot in Spain’s capital, be sure to pack your walking shoes. Get ready to explore one of Spain’s most cultural cities.
Exploring the Attractions There is a lot to see and do in Madrid, but luckily everything is located relatively close together in the city center. That’s not to say that you won’t be walking at least 15,000 steps a day.</description></item><item><title>Valparaíso, Chile</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/valparaiso/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/valparaiso/</guid><description>Valpo/Viña, Chile March 2020
Street Art Capital of Chile When traveling to Chile, don’t miss out on the exciting costal cities of Valparaíso and Viña Del Mar. Valparaíso and Viña del Mar are only about 2 hours in bus from Santiago. They are right next to each other, so you can experience them both. Here, you can find miles of beaches, colorful street art, and amazing culture. Welcome to Valparaíso and Viña Del Mar.</description></item><item><title>Copenhagen, Denmark</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/denmark/copenhagen/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/denmark/copenhagen/</guid><description>Copenhagen, Denmark April 2022
Hej! Thinking of taking a trip to Scandinavia? Definitely put Copenhagen, Denmark on your list. I decided to take a solo trip to Copenhagen and Stockholm for a week. I would recommend this trip to all. There is so much to see and experience in these two capital cities.
Copenhagen Card If you are like me, and are traveling alone, and I recommend buying the Copenhagen card.</description></item><item><title>Salamanca, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/salamanca/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/salamanca/</guid><description>Salamanca, Spain August 2022
A Perfect Destination Salamanca is one of the oldest founded cities in Spain and is home to the 3rd oldest university in the world. A little west of Madrid is where you can find this quaint Spanish city. Enjoy the ambiance of this small, historical town while traveling through Spain.
Tourist Treasures Salamanca has been one of my favorite cities in Spain. Its well-maintained historical architecture is incredible to see while roaming through the town.</description></item><item><title>Granada, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/granada/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/granada/</guid><description>Granada, Spain January 2023
Exploring Andalucía Did you know Granada means Pomegranate in English? Welcome to Granada! Granada is located in the southern part of Spain, called Andalucía. Here, you will hear people speaking Spanish! In the tourist center, you can find people who speak English in some shops and restaurants. Granada is home to the most visited attraction in Spain, the Alhambra.
Arriving at Granada Granada is a small city in Spain with a population of only about 200,000.</description></item><item><title>Vicuña, Chile</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/vicunna/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 16:45:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/vicunna/</guid><description>Vicuña, Chile October 2022
Small Town Vibes Feeling adventurous? Take a trip to Vicuña, Valle de Elqui, Chile and find beauty in the little things. In this small town, you can take a breath of fresh Chilean air, explore the region of Pisco, and enjoy a clear starry night!
You have Reached your Destination There are several ways to arrive in Vicuña. Most likely you’ll be arriving from Santiago.
Take a plane: You can take a plane from Santiago to La Serena.</description></item><item><title>Tromso, Norway</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/norway/tromso/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/norway/tromso/</guid><description>Tromso, Norway December 2022
The Most Magical Place on Earth Ever thought about vacationing to one of the most northern points of the world? Well, be sure to consider Tromso, Norway. I can not say enough incredible things about this small Scandinavian town. It is like driving around in a postcard. Every where you look, you are in nature’s paradise. Welcome to Tromso, Norway.
Timing is Key In Tromso, the time of the year you travel is key.</description></item><item><title>Strasbourg, France</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/strasbourg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/strasbourg/</guid><description>Strasbourg, France January 2023
Weekend in Strasbourg Looking for a short, quiet get away after your jam-packed trip to Paris? Look no more. Take a short 2 hour train ride from Paris to Strasbourg! You can spend 2-3 days in Strasbourg. This small town has everything you need to take the weekend to relax and enjoy the scenery.
Strolling through Strasbourg Unlike Paris, there are very few tourist attractions to see in Strasbourg.</description></item><item><title>Paris, France</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/paris/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/paris/</guid><description>Paris, France January 2023
Exploring Paris Welcome to Paris! The city of love. The fashion capital of the world. The home of delicious pastries, the Eiffel Tower, and tons of museums. For this trip, you need about 4-6 days. Pack your bags and Bon Vonyage!
Best Views in Paris The best views of the city come from 2 places:
Lafayette Partners: This is a huge department store. Skip the shopping and go straight to the terrace!</description></item><item><title>London, England</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/england/london/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/england/london/</guid><description>London, England December 2022
London Here We Come Welcome to London! Start practicing your British accent and touch up on your British English dialect. Pro tip: Chips are French Fries and the lift is the elevator! I recommend at least 5 days in the city. London is a city that you can visit many times and always see something new.
The Underground, AKA: The Subway No need to fear! London is connected through undergrounds and busses!</description></item><item><title>Chile</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:01:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/</guid><description> All Posts Chile Valparaiso Read more about Chile in the city of Valparaiso Read More Vicuña Read more about Chile in the city of Vicuña Read More</description></item><item><title>Denmark</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/denmark/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:01:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/denmark/</guid><description> All Posts Denmark Copenhagen Read more about Denmark in the city of Copenhagen Read More</description></item><item><title>England</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/england/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:01:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/england/</guid><description> All Posts England London Read more about England in the city of London Read More</description></item><item><title>France</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:01:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/</guid><description> All Posts France Paris Read more about France in the city of Paris Read More Strasbourg Read more about France in the city of Strasbourg Read More</description></item><item><title>Norway</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/norway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:01:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/norway/</guid><description> All Posts Norway Tromso Read more about Norway in the city of Tromso Read More</description></item><item><title>Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 10:01:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/</guid><description> All Posts Spain Granada Read more about Spain in the city of Granada Read More Madrid Read more about Spain in the city of Madrid Read More Salamanca Read more about Spain in the city of Salamanca Read More</description></item><item><title>Categories</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/categories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/categories/</guid><description>categories</description></item><item><title>Country</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/country/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/country/</guid><description>Pais de visitas</description></item></channel></rss>