<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trip on Bird’s Eye View</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/categories/trip/</link><description>Recent content in Trip on Bird’s Eye View</description><image><title>Bird’s Eye View</title><url>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/img/birdeyeview.jpg</url><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/img/birdeyeview.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 10:30:30 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/categories/trip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prague, Czech Republic</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/czechrepublic/prague/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/czechrepublic/prague/</guid><description>Prague, Czech Republic Travel date October 2023 Check other cities in Czech Republic Welcome to Prague, located in the heart of Europe. This beautiful city will leave you impressed as you explore its marvelous architecture and unique history. Get lost walking through the streets to experience what this cute city has to offer.
Prague is a rather small city; therefore, you only need about 2 to 3 days to see the top attractions.</description></item><item><title>Berlin, Germany</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/germany/berlin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/germany/berlin/</guid><description>Berlin, Germany Travel date October 2023 Check other cities in Germany Welcome to Deutschland! Berlin is the capital city of Germany, filled with fun, adventure, and a unique culture. If you are a history geek like me, you will intently fall in love with Berlin. Most of my recommendations will be geared towards the history nerds because I believe that this is what makes Berlin such a great city to visit.</description></item><item><title>Barcelona, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/barcelona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/barcelona/</guid><description>Barcelona, Spain Travel date October 2023 Check other cities in Spain Welcome to Barcelona, one of the most explored cities of Spain! Be prepared, Barcelona is huge! You’ll need at least a few days to truly soak it all in. Sit back, relax, and enjoy the journey.
The Arrival You’ll most likely be arriving at Barcelona’s airport. To get to the city center, you have a few options. You can either take the A2 bus, the L9S metro, or the R2N train.</description></item><item><title>Gibraltar, UK</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/uk/gibraltar/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/uk/gibraltar/</guid><description>Gibraltar, UK Travel date May 2023 Check other cities in United Kingdom Looking to check two countries off in one European trip? While in Spain, head down south to Gibraltar, a commonwealth of England. Gibraltar is 3 hours from Granada, 2 hours from Malaga, and about 7 hours from Madrid (all in car). I recommend taking a day trip while in Andalucía to see what the city is all about.</description></item><item><title>Bilbao, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/bilbao/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/bilbao/</guid><description>Bilbao, Spain Travel date May 2023 Check other cities in Spain Did you know that Bilbao has 2 official languages? Here you will find people speaking Spanish AND Basque (Euskera). The Basque language is very different from Spanish and any other language. But, no worries. Everyone in the city center will also speak Spanish and some even English. So… pack your bags and welcome to Bilbao.
Arrival Welcome to Bilbao Bilbao is in the north of Spain, about 400 kilometers from Madrid.</description></item><item><title>Malaga, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/malaga/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/malaga/</guid><description>Málaga, Spain Travel date May 2023 Check other cities in Spain ¡Bienvenidos a Málaga! Welcome to Málaga! The birthplace of Pablo Picasso! Spend about 2 days exploring this fantastic Andalusian city. Enjoy the seafood, paella, and everything else that this city has to offer.
Travel in Málaga Airport Málaga has an international airport! The airport is located about 20 minutes outside of Málaga center. There is a train (Renfe C1) or bus (Alsa) that can take you to the center from the airport.</description></item><item><title>Vienna, Austria</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/austria/vienna/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/austria/vienna/</guid><description>Vienna, Austria Travel date October 2021 Check other cities in Austria WARNING: There are no kangaroos in Austria
Welcome to AUSTRIA, not Australia. Don’t expect to see any kangaroos crossing the street. You are about to explore the birthplace of classical music and the home to incredible artistic culture. Welcome to Wien! (Which is German for Vienna)
Transportation Vienna is conveniently connected by several lines of trams, metros, and buses.</description></item><item><title>Chicago, USA</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/usa/chicago/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/usa/chicago/</guid><description>Chicago, USA Travel date April 2023 Check other cities in USA The Windy City Welcome to the Windy City, Chicago. Chicago is the 3rd largest city in the United States. Plan on spending at least a few days in Chicago to really absorb all the glory the city has to offer.
TIP: Chicago is known for its freezing winters and its hot summers. Be sure to check the weather before making your trip!</description></item><item><title>San Diego, USA</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/usa/sandiego/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/usa/sandiego/</guid><description>San Diego, USA Travel date January 2021 Check other cities in USA Sunshine State Welcome to San Diego! San Diego is by far one of my favorite cities in the United States. If you’re like me, looking for an escape from the freezing winter weather, head on over to the West Coast. Enjoy delicious food, sunshine, great beaches, and interesting culture.
San Diego Arriving in San Diego When arriving at the airport of San Diego, take the City Bus Public transit from the airport to downtown San Diego.</description></item><item><title>Santiago, Chile</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/santiago/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/santiago/</guid><description>Santiago, Chile Travel date October 2022 Check other cities in Chile Why not stay a while? Welcome to the capital of Chile, Santiago. No matter where you plan to travel within Chile, you will most likely always pass through Santiago. Why not stay a few days to explore?
Transportation in Santiago The best way to get around Santiago is by the subway. There are plenty of different subway lines that will get you to anywhere you need to go within the city.</description></item><item><title>Madrid, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/madrid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/madrid/</guid><description>Madrid, Spain Travel date August 2022 Check other cities in Spain Capital of Spain Bienvenidos a Madrid! As you step foot in Spain’s capital, be sure to pack your walking shoes. Get ready to explore one of Spain’s most cultural cities.
Exploring the Attractions There is a lot to see and do in Madrid, but luckily everything is located relatively close together in the city center. That’s not to say that you won’t be walking at least 15,000 steps a day.</description></item><item><title>Valparaíso, Chile</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/valparaiso/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/valparaiso/</guid><description>Valpo/Viña, Chile Travel date March 2020 Check other cities in Chile Street Art Capital of Chile When traveling to Chile, don’t miss out on the exciting coastal cities of Valparaíso and Viña Del Mar. Valparaíso and Viña del Mar are only about 2 hours in bus from Santiago. They are right next to each other, so you can experience them both. Here, you can find miles of beaches, colorful street art, and amazing culture.</description></item><item><title>Copenhagen, Denmark</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/denmark/copenhagen/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/denmark/copenhagen/</guid><description>Copenhagen, Denmark Travel date April 2022 Check other cities in Denmark Hej! Thinking of taking a trip to Scandinavia? Definitely put Copenhagen, Denmark on your list. I decided to take a solo trip to Copenhagen and Stockholm for a week. I would recommend this trip to all. There is so much to see and experience in these two capital cities.
Copenhagen Card If you are like me, and are traveling alone, and I recommend buying the Copenhagen card.</description></item><item><title>Salamanca, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/salamanca/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/salamanca/</guid><description>Salamanca, Spain Travel date August 2022 Check other cities in Spain A Perfect Destination Salamanca is one of the oldest founded cities in Spain and is home to the 3rd oldest university in the world. A little west of Madrid is where you can find this quaint Spanish city. Enjoy the ambiance of this small, historical town while traveling through Spain.
Tourist Treasures Salamanca has been one of my favorite cities in Spain.</description></item><item><title>Granada, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/granada/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/granada/</guid><description>Granada, Spain Travel date January 2023 Check other cities in Spain Exploring Andalucía Did you know Granada means Pomegranate in English? Welcome to Granada! Granada is located in the southern part of Spain, called Andalucía. Here, you will hear people speaking Spanish! In the tourist center, you can find people who speak English in some shops and restaurants. Granada is home to the most visited attraction in Spain, the Alhambra.</description></item><item><title>Vicuña, Chile</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/vicunna/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 16:45:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/chile/vicunna/</guid><description>Vicuña, Chile Travel date October 2022 Check other cities in Chile Small Town Vibes Feeling adventurous? Take a trip to Vicuña, Valle de Elqui, Chile and find beauty in the little things. In this small town, you can take a breath of fresh Chilean air, explore the region of Pisco, and enjoy a clear starry night!
You have Reached your Destination There are several ways to arrive in Vicuña. Most likely you’ll be arriving from Santiago.</description></item><item><title>Tromso, Norway</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/norway/tromso/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/norway/tromso/</guid><description>Tromso, Norway Travel date December 2022 Check other cities in Norway The Most Magical Place on Earth Ever thought about vacationing to one of the most northern points of the world? Well, be sure to consider Tromso, Norway. I can not say enough incredible things about this small Scandinavian town. It is like driving around in a postcard. Every where you look, you are in nature’s paradise. Welcome to Tromso, Norway.</description></item><item><title>Strasbourg, France</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/strasbourg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/strasbourg/</guid><description>Strasbourg, France Travel date January 2023 Check other cities in France Weekend in Strasbourg Looking for a short, quiet get away after your jam-packed trip to Paris? Look no more. Take a short 2 hour train ride from Paris to Strasbourg! You can spend 2-3 days in Strasbourg. This small town has everything you need to take the weekend to relax and enjoy the scenery.
Strolling through Strasbourg Unlike Paris, there are very few tourist attractions to see in Strasbourg.</description></item><item><title>Paris, France</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/paris/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/france/paris/</guid><description>Paris, France Travel date January 2023 Check other cities in France Exploring Paris Welcome to Paris! The city of love. The fashion capital of the world. The home of delicious pastries, the Eiffel Tower, and tons of museums. For this trip, you need about 4-6 days. Pack your bags and Bon Vonyage!
Best Views in Paris The best views of the city come from 2 places:
Lafayette Partners: This is a huge department store.</description></item><item><title>London, UK</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/uk/london/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/uk/london/</guid><description>London, England Travel date December 2022 Check other cities in United Kingdom London Here We Come Welcome to London! Start practicing your British accent and touch up on your British English dialect. Pro tip: Chips are French Fries and the lift is the elevator! I recommend at least 5 days in the city. London is a city that you can visit many times and always see something new.
The Underground, AKA: The Subway No need to fear!</description></item></channel></rss>