<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Spain on Bird’s Eye View</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/tags/spain/</link><description>Recent content in Spain on Bird’s Eye View</description><image><url>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/img/01chile/01la_serena.jpg</url><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/img/01chile/01la_serena.jpg</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/tags/spain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Madrid, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/madrid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/madrid/</guid><description>Madrid, Spain August 2022
Capital of Spain Bienvenidos a Madrid! As you step foot in Spain’s capital, be sure to pack your walking shoes. Get ready to explore one of Spain’s most cultural cities.
Exploring the Attractions There is a lot to see and do in Madrid, but luckily everything is located relatively close together in the city center. That’s not to say that you won’t be walking at least 15,000 steps a day.</description></item><item><title>Salamanca, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/salamanca/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/salamanca/</guid><description>Salamanca, Spain August 2022
A Perfect Destination Salamanca is one of the oldest founded cities in Spain and is home to the 3rd oldest university in the world. A little west of Madrid is where you can find this quaint Spanish city. Enjoy the ambiance of this small, historical town while traveling through Spain.
Tourist Treasures Salamanca has been one of my favorite cities in Spain. Its well-maintained historical architecture is incredible to see while roaming through the town.</description></item><item><title>Granada, Spain</title><link>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/granada/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://blogbirdeyeview.github.io/posts/spain/granada/</guid><description>Granada, Spain January 2023
Exploring Andalucía Did you know Granada means Pomegranate in English? Welcome to Granada! Granada is located in the southern part of Spain, called Andalucía. Here, you will hear people speaking Spanish! In the tourist center, you can find people who speak English in some shops and restaurants. Granada is home to the most visited attraction in Spain, the Alhambra.
Arriving at Granada Granada is a small city in Spain with a population of only about 200,000.</description></item></channel></rss>